Free Consultations  |  Phones Answered 24/7

Free Consultations  |  Phones Answered 24/7

Committed to helping you _heal_ while we recover.

1. [Home](https://www.pendergastlaw.com/)
 » Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy sets out how Pendergast Law uses and protects any information given when you use this website. Information you provide through this website will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Pendergast Law will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. Pendergast Law may change this privacy policy by updating this page.

**INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT**

You may choose to provide us with information that allows you to be identified as a particular person, such as your name, contact telephone numbers, email address, home and/or work address, and legal service enquiries.

Information we collect is used only for responding to your inquiries and otherwise corresponding with you, for processing transactions you request and for the administration, review and/or the improvement the content of the website.  This information is not sold or shared with any outside third party.

As you navigate within our website, we may be collecting and tracking personal information, either by asking you to tell us something about yourself (such as your name, address or email address) or by using data-tracking software that tells us what parts of the website you have browsed. We may collect other information about you, such as your IP address, geographic information, the type of the web browser and operating system you use, and any other information that your web browsing software or Internet Service Provider automatically provides to us. We may be collecting and tracking information about your activities on our website. We may also use “cookies” to keep track of our visitors. You agree that we may aggregate any information which we collect or maintain, and that we may use such aggregated information for internal analysis or for marketing purposes. We may disclose aggregate, de-identified data (i.e. stripped of information that identifies you) to third parties in connection with such analysis and/or marketing. By using our website, you expressly consent to the collection and use of the limited information identified.

**SECURITY**

Pendergast Law is committed to ensuring that information transferred through the internet is secure.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and when we receive it.

Steps are taken to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of personally-identifiable information collected through this website; suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been put in place to safeguard and secure information collected online.

We may disclose your information to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries; (3) comply with valid legal process; (4) protect our rights or property; or (5) facilitate your request for a free case evaluation.

**WEBSITE LINKS**

Pendergast Law’s website may contain links to other websites of interest. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over other websites. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. External websites are not governed by this privacy statement.

We partner with Thomson Reuters, who might also collect data as part of our marketing efforts. To learn more about the Thomson Reuters privacy policy and the data that might be collected, please visit: [Thomson Reuters Privacy Statement](https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/privacy-statement/).

How Can We Help You?
--------------------

Free Consultation
-----------------

Office Location
---------------

555 South Renton Village Place  
Suite 640  
Renton, WA 98057

520 Pike Street  
Suite 1015  
Seattle, WA 98101

1145 Broadway  
Suite 1380  
Tacoma, WA 98402

Social Networks
---------------

\*AV®, AV Preeminent®, Martindale-Hubbell Distinguished and Martindale-Hubbell Notable are certification marks used under license in accordance with the Martindale-Hubbell certification procedures, standards and policies. Martindale-Hubbell® is the facilitator of a peer review rating process. Ratings reflect the anonymous opinions of members of the bar and the judiciary. Martindale-Hubbell® Peer Review Ratings™ fall into two categories — legal ability and general ethical standards.

© 2024 [Pendergast Law](https://lawyers.findlaw.com/profile/view/1758527_1) • All Rights Reserved

[Disclaimer](https://www.pendergastlaw.com/disclaimer/) | [Site Map](https://www.pendergastlaw.com/site-map/) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.pendergastlaw.com/privacy/) | [Business Development Solutions](https://www.findlaw.com/lawyer-marketing/) by [FindLaw](https://www.findlaw.com/), part of Thomson Reuters
